repos.org 2018-09-04

# Repo.com | Privacy Policy

We understand the sensitive nature of privacy issues and we will do our best to ensure that your confidentiality remains protected.

If you simply wish to browse the Repo.com site you will not be required to fill out any personal information form or registration. Any contact, submission or request forms will require you to share personal information such as your name, email address or telephone number.

During your use of our site, we may collect demographic and profile data. This data is used so we may enhance your experience at our site. For example: showing you content that you may be interested in according to your preferences.

At no time will information that personally identifies you be distributed to any third party.

### Coverage

This policy applies to Repo.com. It does not apply to our partners or any other web site that may be connected, in any way, with Repo.com.

### Use of Cookies

We only use cookies to manage account and statistical information. We do not store any private or personal information.

### Children

Repo.com does not sell products for purchase by minors. If you are under 18, we request that you use only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

### Security

Repo.com has taken security measures in effort to protect against the loss, misuse and/or alteration of any customer data under our control. Unfortunately, we are unable to fully guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of the data will not occur. We do promise to do the utmost to prevent against any such occurrences.

### Revisions

Our business is subject to change. This privacy statement may change and use of the information that we gather could also change. Visit our web site frequently to see the most recent privacy policies in operation.

### Contact Us

If you have any concern about privacy at one of our sites, please contact us with your concern, and we will do our best to resolve it in a timely manner.

Repo.com -- We take Care of Unfinished Business TM  
REPO.com -- small enough to care -- LARGE enough to get the job done TM
